<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-06-17T07:11:58-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Pentagons FIghting Polygons</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">WHAMMY!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/06/16/techniques.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WHAMMY!" /><published>2024-06-16T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-06-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/06/16/techniques</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/06/16/techniques.html"><![CDATA[<html>
<head>
<title>Onomatopeia</title>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="/style.css" />
<script src="/assets/script.js"></script>
<style>
    body {
            font-family: 'Franklin Gothic Medium', 'Arial Narrow', Arial, sans-serif;
            background-color: black;
        }
        p {
            color: white;
            font-size: 20px;
        }
        b {
            color: orange;
            font-family: 'Segoe UI', Tahoma, Geneva, Verdana, sans-serif;
        }
        .p2 {
            color: rgb(128, 118, 118);
            font-size: 15px;
            text-align: center;
        }
        .p3 {
            color: orange;
            font-family: 'Trebuchet MS', 'Lucida Sans Unicode', 'Lucida Grande', 'Lucida Sans', Arial, sans-serif;
        }
        h1 {
            color: red;
            font-size: 50px;
            text-align: left;
            padding-left: 35px;
            font-family: Impact, Haettenschweiler, 'Arial Narrow Bold', sans-serif;
        }
        h3 {
            color: red;
            font-size: 60px;
            text-align: left;
            padding-left: 35px;
            font-family: Impact, Haettenschweiler, 'Arial Narrow Bold', sans-serif;
        }
</style>
</head>
    
<img src="/assets/naked_women.gif" width="470" height="300" alt="nakedness" />
<body>

 <p>Boom! Bang! Pop! Whammy!</p>  
 <p2>Onomatopoeia is a word or group of words that, when spoken aloud, imitates the sound it produces.</p2>
 <p2>Roy Lichtenstein was an artist who mastered panting with his medium of pointillism creating artwork that used thousands of dots and lines to create large paintings of onomatopeas</p2>  
 <p2><b>"boom"</b>, <b>"whammy"</b>and my all time favorite<b>"pop!"</b>
 <p2>Below is one of Roy's famous paintings showing the onomatopoeia word, <p2><b>"CRACK"</b></p2></p2>
 <p2>. . . . </p2>
<img src="/assets/crackRoyLict.jpeg" width="470" height="300" alt="love-writing" /> 


<h3>Rhetoric</h3>

      To tell a tale that tantalizes the throngs, try alliteration, whichi refers to using the same sound, usually a consonant, at the beginning of words near each other in a sentence. 

<img src="/assets/roypointalism.jpg" width="470" height="300" alt="pointalism" />


<!--Yea this html above looks pretty rough so we can fix this next time we work dis -->
<body>
    <h1>Example Heading</h1>
    <p>Example paragraph.</p>
    <p class="p2">Another paragraph with class p2.</p>
    <p class="p3">Another paragraph with class p3.</p>
</body>


&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;
</p2></body></html>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="linguistics" /><category term="self-study" /><category term="beginner" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Onomatopeia]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Toe-Touching with Rubys &amp;amp; Ruby on Rails</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/post/2024/06/03/toe-touch.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Toe-Touching with Rubys &amp;amp; Ruby on Rails" /><published>2024-06-03T09:44:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-06-03T09:44:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/post/2024/06/03/toe-touch</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/post/2024/06/03/toe-touch.html"><![CDATA[<div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>                       🗿👽Toe-Touching ON Rubies &amp; Ruby on Rails 
</code></pre></div></div>

<p>Jekyll is a popular choice for creating static websites. It is easy to use, flexible, and fast-loading websites. It can be customized to create different types of websites as well as provide free hosting with GitHub Pages. In this brief essay we will explore how Jekyll works and its benefits.</p>

<p>Jekyll has become a popular choice for creating static websites. Nobody can beat having no more databases, comment moderation, or pesky updates to install-just your content.</p>

<p>It’s ease of use makes it friendly for new developers to learn with. It’s fast-loading makes it easy to generate fast-loading websites that are loaded quickly. It’s flexible, and ability makes it easy to create different types of websites, such as blog websites, e-commerce websites, and more complex websites with our pre-defined layouts and structures. 
Before you run jekyll we will first have to install all of the following: jekyll, ruby, make, g++, bundler.  After you’ve installed all of these you can run jekyll by typing - jekyll -v, make -v, gcc ++, and bundler -v, ruby -v to see if you have all of these installed.  If not that install them first.</p>

<p>The you will run:</p>

<p><img src="/assets/jekyll.jpg" width="650" height="250" alt="jekyllStart.png" /></p>

<p>Here are some examples of what you can do using Jekyll Static Site Generator.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/jekyllTwitch.jpg" width="650" height="450" alt="jekyllExamples.png" /></p>

<p><img src="/assets/jekyllBitcoin.jpg" width="650" height="450" alt="jekyllExamples.png" /></p>

<p><img src="/assets/jekyllFrench.jpg" width="650" height="450" alt="jekyllExamples.png" /></p>

<p>You can also use GitHub pages to host your website. <a href="https://pages.github.com/">GitHub Pages</a> 
All GitHub Pages builds will use GitHub Actions from June 30, 2024. No other changes are required but GitHub Actions must be enabled in your repository for builds to continue. For more information on enabling GitHub Actions, see “Managing GitHub Actions settings for a repository.”</p>

<p><img src="/assets/githubPages.jpg" width="650" height="600" alt="jekyllGitHub.png" /></p>

<p>Jekyll is not all sunshine and rainbows. The bad news when dealing with jekyll is the following. 
The downside to using Jekyll is that it has limited support for Ruby on Rails. Jekyll also has limited support for interactive elements as well as layouts and support for interactive elements. Accessibility support is also limited. The ways in which the dev is allowed to customize said website is also limited.</p>

<p>All in all jekyll’s website creator is a pretty good tool to use, but if you’re trying to make a more advanced and flashy web site than maybe check out other tools instead. 
Jekyll is also pretty beginner friendly for new developers which makes it nice since you get to see right away what you’re making and how it works.</p>

<p>Check it out. Thanks for reading…</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="post" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[🗿👽Toe-Touching ON Rubies &amp; Ruby on Rails]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Man Who Lived At Warner Bros</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/post/2024/06/03/i-will-not-loose.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Man Who Lived At Warner Bros" /><published>2024-06-03T09:44:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-06-03T09:44:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/post/2024/06/03/i-will-not-loose</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/post/2024/06/03/i-will-not-loose.html"><![CDATA[<p>“Memetic Wizardry of the puppetry marked in chaos with love.” This was the tattoo marked on your mommy.  No regets painted the front collar bone of little Tommy Bundles. 
In life it always seems to be others who assume you’re depressed or that something is wrong. There is always that blind spot held by each and everyone of us humans. To understand the blind spot is to know self. It’s not a question if the blind spot exhists. No it’s not that at all. The blind spot is there and being human guarantees the presence of such a thing regardless.</p>

<p>A man once said, “the man who knows he knows is a fool, shun him. A man who knows he knows not is a student, teach him.”</p>

<p>In this world it’s up to you as to who you become. Before learning to win it’s important we all learn how loose.  Anyone can win a trophy gaining the smiles and energetic applause of others.
Back hidden beyond the line of sight in an alleyway dwarfed by the massive Warner-Brother Studios sat a man pondering his very own life. Often he would enjoy hidding in the hidden parts of the main alleyway that connected to just one of the main WB studios.  Giant buildings with space, room, and the magic of cinema made up the Warner Brother Studios that were nestled down in Whilmington, North Carolina. Nobody really knows this but down there is North Carolina is where Hollywood’s other stages are located.</p>

<p>to be continued….</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="post" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Memetic Wizardry of the puppetry marked in chaos with love.” This was the tattoo marked on your mommy. No regets painted the front collar bone of little Tommy Bundles. In life it always seems to be others who assume you’re depressed or that something is wrong. There is always that blind spot held by each and everyone of us humans. To understand the blind spot is to know self. It’s not a question if the blind spot exhists. No it’s not that at all. The blind spot is there and being human guarantees the presence of such a thing regardless.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">learning while playing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/post/2024/05/26/learning-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="learning while playing" /><published>2024-05-26T21:22:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-05-26T21:22:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/post/2024/05/26/learning-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/post/2024/05/26/learning-post.html"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="post" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Meta Wizard Learning Page</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/05/20/meta-wizard.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Meta Wizard Learning Page" /><published>2024-05-20T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-05-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/05/20/meta-wizard</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/05/20/meta-wizard.html"><![CDATA[<p><em>testing</em></p>

<p><em>mrkdown is great for taking notes and documentation</em></p>

<p>==the double bind will get you ever time==</p>

<p>##this makes text bigger if i remember correctly</p>

<h1 id="_configyml">_config.yml</h1>
<p>title: My Static Site
author: Your Name</p>

<h1 id="site-settings">Site settings</h1>
<p>url: https://example.com
baseurl: “”</p>

<h1 id="pagination">Pagination</h1>
<p>paginate: 5</p>

<h1 id="markdown-engine">Markdown engine</h1>
<p>markdown: kramdown</p>

<h1 id="sass">Sass</h1>
<p>sass:
  sass_dir: assets
  compressed: true</p>]]></content><author><name>Miller Time</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Page-1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/05/18/page1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Page-1" /><published>2024-05-18T01:50:41-04:00</published><updated>2024-05-18T01:50:41-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/05/18/page1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/05/18/page1.html"><![CDATA[<p>!</p>

<p>So this is my first post.  We can now start practicing with jekyll and out writing skills. 
So tomorrow we shall start writing our first post. We will begin this schedule of writing in the mornings one blog poast per day. We must strengthen our writing skills. There are 2 types of people. Those who can write and those who can not. As well as there are those who can weld and those who can not. I wish to learn how to write in jekyll as well as in markdown.  I know markdown fairly well but I wish to learn how to write in jekyll. I also wish to learn how to write better like my friend Abigail.  One of the best writers i know. Sure we won’t be as good as she is, but we can learn better comma placement as well as better NGP techniques and more.
Knowing how to write a good story that is able to grab the reader and place them in another place of their own mind is something we wish to master. The power of writing is something that has always been a part of my life.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/05/18/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2024-05-18T01:50:41-04:00</published><updated>2024-05-18T01:50:41-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/05/18/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/05/18/welcome-to-jekyll.html"><![CDATA[<p>You’ll find this post in your <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_posts</code> directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">jekyll serve</code>, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</p>

<p>Jekyll requires blog post files to be named according to the following format:</p>

<p><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">YEAR-MONTH-DAY-title.MARKUP</code></p>

<p>Where <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">YEAR</code> is a four-digit number, <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">MONTH</code> and <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">DAY</code> are both two-digit numbers, and <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">MARKUP</code> is the file extension representing the format used in the file. After that, include the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.</p>

<p>Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:</p>

<figure class="highlight"><pre><code class="language-ruby" data-lang="ruby"><span class="k">def</span> <span class="nf">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="p">)</span>
  <span class="nb">puts</span> <span class="s2">"Hi, </span><span class="si">#{</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="si">}</span><span class="s2">"</span>
<span class="k">end</span>
<span class="n">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="s1">'Tom'</span><span class="p">)</span>
<span class="c1">#=&gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.</span></code></pre></figure>

<p>Check out the <a href="https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home">Jekyll docs</a> for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at <a href="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll’s GitHub repo</a>. If you have questions, you can ask them on <a href="https://talk.jekyllrb.com/">Jekyll Talk</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">black-and-gold</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/05/18/black-and-gold.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="black-and-gold" /><published>2024-05-18T01:50:41-04:00</published><updated>2024-05-18T01:50:41-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/05/18/black-and-gold</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/05/18/black-and-gold.html"><![CDATA[<p>There are somethings done</p>

<p>in the midnight son</p>

<p>by the men who wear black and gold</p>

<p>whose secret tails leave secret trails</p>

<p>that will make your blood run cold.</p>

<p>The queerest day evil ever did see</p>

<p>was the day they left</p>

<p>the SIG by the sea…</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are somethings done]]></summary></entry></feed>